把我弄爽点 老兄
Oh, you got to really get it up in there, dawg.
前情提要
有些罪孽应该受到永恒的诅咒
Some sins deserve eternal damnation.
我犯下了谋杀罪
I've committed murders.
囚犯拒绝探视
Inmate refused visitation.
不
No!
是惊恐发作 不管你在做什么 停下来
A panic attack. Whatever you're doing, stop it.
他们杀了卡梅隆科尔曼 因为他们认为他是泄密者 我受够了
They killed Cameron Coleman because they thought that he was the fucking leak. I'm done.
卡梅隆科尔曼并不是泄密者
Cameron Coleman wasn't the leak.
所以 要么智者在骗你 要么她就像老鼠的乳头一样毫无用处
So, either Sage was lying to you, or she's as useless as tits on a mouse.
我愿意为您做任何事
I'd do anything for you.
我的乖男孩
That's my boy.
我恨你
I hate you.
喜美子
Kimiko!
维多利亚是这个计划中 不可或缺的一部分
Victoria here, she's an integral part of the plan.
我们将在选举被获准后处理辛格尔
We'll handle Singer after the election's certified.
第二十五项法案被实施时 你需要合理的推诿
We need plausible deniability when the 25th is invoked.
你说的可是一场政变啊
You're talking about a coup.
列出一份清单 告诉我们提取病毒都需要什么
You give us a list of what you need to extract the virus, and make it
提高病毒的强度 足以杀掉祖国人才行
strong enough to top Homelander.
我们说的不是杀死祖国人而已
We're not just talking about killing Homelander,
而是杀掉地球上的每一个超人类
we're talking about killing every Supe on Earth.
没人说过要搞种族灭绝
No one ever said nothing about genocide.
这他妈的是什么意思 你就是我
What the fuck's that supposed to mean, "you're me"?
注射过五号之后 你的大脑里 长出了一个大大的肿瘤 你个混蛋
You got a big old fat V'd-up brain tumor, you cunt,
所以你才看得到我
which is why you are seeing me in the first place.
我就是你
I am you.
沃特工作室呈现
《纽约市五号大道》圣诞特辑
圣诞快乐 火车头
Well, Merry Christmas, A-Train!
圣诞快乐 莱恩
Oh, Merry Christmas, Ryan.
为什么不开心
Why the long face?
反法西斯行动
Antifa.
那是什么
What's that?
莱恩 这个词形容 讨厌超级英雄和美国
Well, Ryan, it's a word for people who hate superheroes and America
甚于讨厌圣诞节的人
even more than they hate Christmas.
他们长什么样  -那就是问题所在
Well, what do they look like?  -That's the problem.
他们可能是任何人
They can look like anyone,
你的邻居 你的老师
your neighbors, your teachers,
甚至你的爸妈
even your mom and dad.
♪ When you see something, say something ♪
发现可疑情况就举报
? When you see something, say something ?
♪ Report that groomer when he comes for you ♪
有人想要操控你 举报他
? Report that groomer when he comes for you ?
♪ See something, say something ♪
发现可疑情况就举报
? See something, say something ?
♪ 'Cause he hates America and Christmas, too ♪
因为他也讨厌美国和圣诞节
? 'Cause he hates America and Christmas, too ?
♪ It's the woke principal and his husband Chad ♪
可能是左翼的校长和他丈夫查德
? It's the woke principal and his husband Chad ?
♪ Or it could be your uncle who says Supes are bad ♪
也可能是你说超人类坏话的叔叔
? Or it could be your uncle who says Supes are bad ?
♪ It might even be your mom and your dad ♪
甚至可能是你的爸妈 但请听听黄金法则
? It might even be your mom and your dad ?
汤米 可以暂停一下吗  -暂停排练
Uh, Tommy, can we cut out for a second?  -Uh, that's a cut on rehearsal.
停  -好
That's a cut.
各位 休息20分钟
Back in 20, everyone.
没什么事吧
Hey, is everything okay?
让孩子们去举报自己的父母 这也...
I mean, yeah, it's just... we're telling kids to report on their own parents.
你爸已经批准这些歌词了
The lyrics were approved by your dad.
亲自批准的 所以...
Personally, so...
对哦 是哈  -对
Right. Right, yeah, yeah.  -Right.
没问题
Yeah. It's no problem.
我得去趟洗手间
I just need to go 10-1.
好
Yeah.
黑袍纠察队
第四季 第七集
公关部向犹太教会道歉了
PR made that apology to Temple Beth El,
所以这事已经板上钉钉了
so that should be a done fucking deal.
其次 我们有个很好的...
Um, secondly, we've got a...
不是11点开会吗
I thought the meeting started at 11:00.
我们提前开了
We moved it up.
下一项
Um, next.
营销部想开始出售你的非同质化代币
Oh, marketing would like to start selling these NFTs of you.
显然 买家不只是购买图片文件 还会加入虚拟社区
Apparently, you're not just buying JPEGs, you're joining a community.
艾诗丽  -是 先生
Ashley.  -Yes, sir?
出去  -是 先生
Get out.  -Yes, sir.
对不起 先生 是 没问题
Sorry, sir. Yes, absolutely.
智者
Sage...
泄密者是谁
who's the leak?
我们正在调查
We're making inquiries.
需要花点时间
It's a process,
我们需要...
we're eliminating--
我想你很清楚这是什么
I assume you know what that is.
是监听器  -威廉布彻尔布下的监听器
It's a bug.  -Specifically William Butcher's bug.
我们在泰克骑士庄园说的每一个字 他们可能都听到了
They probably heard every single word we said at Tek-Knight's.
很可能还杀了他
And likely killed him.
他们不会公开这些信息
They won't go public with the information.
为什么呢
And why not?  -Because it would short-circuit
因为会妨碍他们得到自己想要的东西
everything they really want,
他们想一劳永逸地 神不知鬼不觉地除掉纽曼
which is to quietly take out Neuman once and for all.
我们应该把布彻尔及其整个团队 都杀个片甲不留
We should slaughter Butcher and his whole fucking team.
真是个好主意 先生
Now that is a great idea, sir.
反正布彻尔也活不了几个月了
Butcher will be dead in a few months anyway.
就要实行大计划了
And this close to go-time,
我可不想引起中情局的注意  -是的
I wouldn't stir up shit with the CIA.  -Yes, yes, yes.
你那该死的杰出计划
Your illustrious fucking plan.
我们无缘无故地杀了卡梅隆科尔曼
We killed Cameron Coleman for no reason.
暂时的困难 但无碍于计划
A speed bump but, ultimately, harmless.
卡梅隆和迈克林德尔一起打高尔夫球
Cameron golfed with Mike Lindell,
后者撤走了 价值五千万美元的枕头广告投资
who just pulled 50 million bucks worth of pillow commercials.
那叫无碍吗
You call that harmless?
看看是谁在赶鸭子上架做算数呢
Oh, look at Daisy Duck Dynasty doing math.
我和鞭炮讨论来着
You know, Firecracker and I have been talking.
肯定相当刺激
Stimulating, I'm sure.
对不起
Sorry.
你有头脑 智者
You have brains, Sage,
但我有智慧
but I have wisdom.
如果你的大脑再次受伤
And what happens if those brains of yours get blown out again,
让你像个胡言乱语的白痴怎么办
leaving you talking like a gibbering idiot?
我和鞭炮会找出泄密者
Firecracker and I will find the leak.
恕我直言 上次...  -宽恕你
With respect, the last time---Respect?
我没感觉你在寻求宽恕
I don't hear no fucking respect.
事实上 你对这位伟大人物这么讲话
In fact, I am personally offended
令我个人感到极受冒犯
by the way you are talking to this great man.
你专心管好枪手就行了
You just focus on the shooter,
确保他六号那天准备就绪
make sure he's good to go on the sixth.
他会准备好的
He'll be ready.
好的
Good.
你可以离开了
You may leave.
《静水深流》 深海的诗
这首叫《世界是我们的牡蛎》
This one's called The World's Our Oyster.
“闪闪发光的海带森林
"Shimmering forests of kelp
“就像大自然的洗车刷
Like nature's car wash brushes
“在黑暗的海底 水母发光
At the dark bottom, jellyfish glow
“就像兄弟会的熔岩灯
Like frat house lava lamps
“我可以带你游去任何地方
I can swim you anywhere
“七大洋 水路长长”
The seven seas, one big wet road."
天哪 凯文
Jesus, Kevin.
你确实有着诗人的灵魂
You really have the soul of a poet.
好啦
Stop.
你真坏
You're so bad.
天哪 你的舌头就像舷外发动机
And, God, your tongue is like an outboard motor.
是吗
Yeah?
我高潮了好多次
I came so many times.
真的吗
Really?
今天不顺 刺我的大脑 然后从后面干我
我...
I, uh,
我得走了 宝贝
I got to go, babe.
什么 这就走
What? You do?
职责在身
Duty calls.
等等 不 等等
Wait. No, no. Wait.
拜托 宝贝 你知道 自己不能长时间离开水
Come on, babe. You know you can't be out of water for long.
不 你答应过我 会把我放进床上方的水族箱
No, you promised me you'd move me into the tank above the bed.
没错 当然可以 宝贝
Right, no. Of course, babe.
一定会的
A hunny percent.
只不过 我得先清除淡水外来物种
I just got to, uh, you know, clear out the freshwater exotics first,
然后就一切就绪...对了 我要跟希安开电话会议 给他的新作
and then it'll be all set. Oh, and I got a notes call with Shia
《蜜糖男孩二》改剧本
on his new draft of Honey Boy 2.
肯定很精彩
It's really starting to sing.
那我明天可以搬进去吗
Well, can I move in tomorrow?
完全可以
Yeah, totally.
你这么一说 我就得收拾东西离开
Just like that, I'm supposed to pick up and leave?
在沙漠里过圣诞节 太棒了
Christmas in the desert. Terrific.
跟詹待在塞多纳你会更安全 好吗
You're safer with Gen in Sedona, okay?
可能...很快就有大事发生
Some... things might happen soon.
什么意思 什么事
What do you mean? What... what kind of things?
你还是不知道的好  -你突然打给我...
It's better you don't know.  -You call me out of the blue--
几个星期以来 我每天都给你打电话
I have called you every day for weeks.
今天你才接
This is the first time you've picked up.
他们不让我参加周二的圣经小组了
You know, they kicked me out of the Tuesday Bible group.
与我无关  -是吗
That has nothing to do with me.  -No?
我听见雪莉低声说 “唐娜怎么会养出那种女儿 ”
Well, I heard Shelly whisper, "How the heck did Donna raise that girl?"
你明天一早出发就好
Okay, just hit the road first thing tomorrow--
“她怎么做得出堕胎这种事 ”
"That she would have an abortion?"
你应该达到更高的标准
You're supposed to be held to a higher standard.
我是按高标准养育你的
That's how I raised you.
全世界的女孩以你为榜样
Girls all over the world look up to you.
现在她们认为自己可以为所欲为了 因为没有任何后果
And now they think they can be loose, because there's no consequences--
那不关你的事
That is none of your business,
肯定也他妈的不关雪莉的事
and it sure as fuck isn't Shelly's.
你是星光 你是位超级英雄
You're Starlight. You're a superhero.
我是个人
I'm a person.
现在 星光之类的屁事已经不重要了
Right now, none of that Starlight shit matters.
那休伊为什么留着你的战衣
Then why did Hughie save the suit?
我非常 非常抱歉
I am so, so sorry.
真他妈糟透了
That is so fucked.
我从垃圾桶里捡回来的 以为某天你可能会后悔扔掉它
I pulled it from the trash. I mean, I thought you might regret tossing it someday.
我连看都不想看  -好的
I don't even like looking at it.  -Okay.
好吧
All right.
好了 我...这就扔掉
Done. I am--There it goes.
它...
It is...
滚蛋了
out of here.
我只是...
I just...
天哪 我只是...不想
God. I just, I didn't...
让宝宝降生到一个面临末日的世界
want to bring a baby into a world that's ending.
休伊 这种事...
Hughie. It's just...
这种事令人难以承受
...it's just all too much.
到处都一片混乱 情况失控
I mean, there are so many fucking dumpster fires.
我们要从哪里入手呢
Where do we even start?
一步一步来吧
We just take it step by step.
你一直在喝酒  -我不知道你想怎样
You smell like you've been drinking.  -I don't know what you want from me, all right?
我马上就赶来了
I got here as fast as I could--
我希望你干好这一票  -无所谓了
I want you to do your fucking job.  -Whatever.
你真的认为他就是枪手
You really think this could be our Lee Harvey?
火车头说是他
That's what A-Train says.
要我说 我们也去会会他
I say we visit him, too.
你他妈的去哪了  -蹲厕所里拉屎啊
Where the fuck you been?  -Shittin' a kidney.
好吧 听着
All right, listen up.
别不开心 但是
Now, don't get your knickers in a twist, but...
你们还记得纽曼的心上人吧 造病毒的那小子
...you remember Neuman's dearly departed virus bloke?
萨米尔沙阿博士
Dr. Sameer Shah?
我是认真的 布彻尔 别
I'm serious, Butcher. Don't.
有意思的是
Well, funny story.
原来他还没死
Turns out he ain't that dead.
他一直在为我工作 制造更多的病毒
He's been working for me, making some more of that virus.
搞什么  -等等 他们只发现了...
What the fuck?  -Wait, all they found was--
天哪 你个混蛋
Goddamn it, you asshole.
你砍断了他的腿
Did you cut off his leg?
冷静点
All right, all right, keep your hair on.
你把人家截了肢
So, basically, you've been amputatin' motherfuckers
让他研究秘密生物武器
while working on a secret bioweapon,
却要我们冷静
and we're the ones that are supposed to chill?
你会毁了我们最好的机会
You are pissing away our best shot.
问题是 我们遇到了一个小障碍
Now, the trouble is, we've hit a slight snag.
如果病毒能干掉祖国人
He can't make it deadly enough to top Homelander
就会造成全球性的大瘟疫
without causing a, you know, global pandemic.
天哪
Jesus.
等等
Wait.
种族灭绝
Genocide.
你说的是超人类的种族灭绝...
You're talking about Supe genocide. That's--
布彻尔 即使对你这种人来说 这也...
Yeah, Butcher, even for you--
所以我才告诉你们 不是吗
Which is why I'm fucking telling you, innit?
你以为我想让双手沾满鲜血吗
You think I want that much blood on me hands?
你想 你他妈的想在血海里游泳
Yeah, you do. You want to fucking swim in it.
不 我不想
No, I don't.
No, I do not.
因此 为了防止病毒 像野火燎原一样灭了你们超人类
So, to keep the bug from burning through you lot like wildfire,
我觉得萨米尔需要一点帮助
I thought ol' Sameer could do with a bit of a hand.
谁的帮助
From who?
真是极富有洞察力 与话题密切相关的问题 小子
A question both insightful and germane, my son.
他来了
Ah, here he is.
说曹操 曹操就到
Speak of the devil.
早上好
Bonjour.
你他妈的是怎么出狱的
How the fuck did you get out?
我让马洛里找了几个熟人
I had Mallory pull a few strings.
得说清楚 这是违背我意愿的
Just to be clear, this was against my will.
我宁愿操一罐鱼饵 也不想出狱
I'd rather fuck a jar of fishing lures than to be free.
真不赖
Oh, cool. Cool.
好吧 重聚愉快
All right, then. Happy reunions.
法兰奇会帮忙拣选病毒
So, Frenchie will help sort the virus.
只给祖国人和副总统注射病毒 其他人不会受影响
We'll use it on Homelander and the VP and that's it, no one else.
你个该死的胆小鬼
You fucking coward.
好的
Okay,
这样可行
that works.
喜美子 法兰奇
Kimiko, Frenchie,
你们俩去帮沙阿博士
you two are on Dr. Shah.
剩下的人去查那个神秘枪手
The rest of you, on the mystery man.
别·做·混蛋
“别做个混蛋”
"Don't be a cunt."
听着 你应该...去
Listen... You should... go on ahead.
那你呢  -我不去
You what?  -Without me.
我得和莫妮克谈谈 是...
I gotta talk to Monique. It's...
得了吧
Oh, come off it.
别让我独自面对这堆混球
Don't leave me alone with this lot.
等等 怎么了
Wait, what?
他不参与行动了  -不参与 为什么
He ain't going. You're not going? Why?
我们要正式宣布
All right, so we gonna make this official?
跪下 我会用鸡巴封你为骑士
Take a knee, I'll knight you with my dick.
你回来领导英雄克星 好吗
You're back in charge of The Boys again, all right?
反正我还是做研究比较好
I'm better off doing research anyway.
不 你不能这样做
No, you can't do this.
你不必这样做
You don't got to do this.
他得这样做 这对我们有好处
Yeah, he does. This is good for us.
不行 这个混蛋不回来 情况就已经很糟糕了
You can't. Things are bad already without this fucking asshole back.
这情况真难搞
Look what I got to deal with.
听着 这事无可争议 伙计们
Listen, it ain't a debate, you guys.
我晕过去了
I passed out.
在执行任务期间
During a mission.
我不适合当头儿
I ain't cut out to be skipper.
他才适合
But he is.
所以让他来当
So, it's him.
你来当
It's you.
就这么办
End of story.
进来 宝贝
Hey, come in, baby.
宝贝
Okay, babe...
给 拿着
Here, take this.
一万美元现金 从我的账户转入你的名下
That's $10,000 cash. The rest of my accounts, I transferred into yours.
马文  -这是两张去伯利兹的单程票
Marvin---Here's two one-way tickets to Belize.
今晚你和珍妮的航班 只是待上一阵子
You and Janine's flights are tonight. Now, it's not forever,
等情况平稳了就回来  -停
just until things blow over.  -Stop.
停下来
Just stop.
好吗
Okay?
告诉我这是怎么回事
Tell me what's wrong.
就要发生大事了
Something big's about to go down.
如果我们输了 世界就会一团糟
If we lose, shit's gonna get crazy.
如果我们赢了 世界就更会是一团糟
If we win, shit's gonna get even crazier,
所以 无论如何 你们都得走
so either way, y'all got to go.
再次让你们收拾东西离开 我很抱歉
And I'm sorry to make you have to pick up and leave again,
但我他妈的得完成任务
but I got one fucking job to do,
这是为了保证你和珍妮的安全
and that's to keep you and Janine safe,
我会良心受遣 如果我任由...
and I'll be damned if I let any of this fucking sh--
我知道你很努力 马文
I know how hard you try, Marvin,
照顾我和珍妮
taking care of Janine and me.
跟我们走吧
Come with us.
我相信你
I believe you.
如果你做了这些事 我...
If you did all this, I...
我确信情况比我想象的还糟
...I'm sure it's even worse than I'm imagining.
所以 我们走吧
So let's go.
我们三个人 我们一家一起走
The three of us, let's go be a family.
莫妮克
Monique...
你知道我最在乎你和珍妮 对吧
you know that you and Janine are my heart, right?
可我不能走  -看看你
I can't.  -Look at you.
那次恐慌发作本该是个警告 马文
That panic attack was supposed to be a warning, Marvin.
在机场跟我们会合
Meet us at the airport...
明天这个时候 宝贝 我们就已经在海滩上喝着朗姆潘趣酒
...and this time tomorrow, baby, we'll be sipping rum punches
看珍妮躲避海浪了
on the beach while Janine dodges the waves.
纪念卡梅隆科尔曼 珍妮麦卡锡说:“又一位烈士离世”
十多年来 他一直都是您可以信赖的声音
For over a decade, one man has been a voice you can trust.
现在 那个声音消逝了
And now that voice is gone.
卡梅隆科尔曼因流感疫苗直接引起的
Cameron Coleman has died of a brain aneurism
脑动脉瘤去世
as a direct result of the flu vaccine.
斯人已逝 永远铭记
Gone from this world, but never gone from our hearts.
再次报道...
Once again, tragedy--
你的助理呢
Hey. What happened to your assistant?
格雷戈里
Oh, Gregory?
我解雇了他 总把我的沙拉订单搞错
I fired him. Dumb fuck could never get my Sweetgreen order right.
你想干什么
What do you want?
听着 他们知道 卡梅隆不是泄密者了...
Listen. They know Cameron's not the leak--
闭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
我不想再听那些屁事了
I don't want to hear that shit anymore.
你他妈的少扯上我 我不干了
You leave me the fuck out of that. I'm done.
你喝醉了
You're shitfaced?
我仍然是这家公司的首席执行官
I am still the CEO of this company,
如果首席执行官想在上午11点 喝个烂醉如泥 谁也管不了
and if the CEO wants to get shitfaced at 11:00 a.m., I can.
他是最好的
He was the best.
他是我最好的助手
He was the fucking best assistant I ever fucking had.
我解雇他 是为了让他离开这个该死的地方
And I fired him to get him away from this fucking place.
我害卡梅隆被杀 是我陷害了他
I had Cameron killed. I had him killed.
你救了我的命
Look, you saved my life.
我本来可以用其他方式救你
I could've done that some other way.
他不必死的
He didn't have to die.
在这里...很容易就会变成禽兽
It's-it's so easy to become a monster around here.
我们当初离开会怎样呢
What if we left? Huh?
What if we left?
你和我
You and me?
我不是说发生性关系 真恶心 不是的
I don't mean us fucking--ew, no.
我在佛罗伦萨上的大三 我们可以一走了之
I spent my junior year abroad in Florence, we could just go, we could go.
你有护照  -好了
You have a passport.  -All right.
你不需要护照  -艾诗丽
Oh, you don't need a passport. You just run---Hey, Ashley. Ashley.
你振作一点 好吗
Get your shit together.
你不能烂醉如泥 口不择言
Okay? You cannot be all wasted running your fucking mouth,
会害死我们俩的
not when you have both of our lives in your fucking hands.
管好你的嘴
Button it up.
现在
Now.
好了 我去后面看看
All right. I'll have a dekko around the back,
你们俩去看看前面 好吗
you two take the front, yeah?
然后我们去找那个枪手
And then we'll pay the shooter a visit.
我绞尽脑汁
You know, I have been racking my brain...
想弄清楚你是什么时候 开始对超人类心软的
trying to figure out when you got this soft spot for Supes.
是你跟梅芙翻云覆雨的时候吗
Was it when you shot your load and cream-pied Maeve?
好吧 知道吗
All right, you know what?
受够你对我的沉默对待了 你个顽固不化的混蛋
Enough with the silent treatment, you stubborn prick,
我们各走各路
I am done fucking around with you.
我知道你不在乎星光或喜美子
See, I know you don't care about Starlight or Kimiko.
并不真的在乎
Not really.
莱恩呢
And Ryan?
他甚至都不是你的种
He's not even yours.
所以 告诉我 为什么对这孩子这么有信心
So, tell me... what justifies the faith in the kid?
我跟她保证过
I gave her my word.
贝嘉
Becca?
真的吗
Really?
如果你的爱如此完美纯洁
If your love was so perfect and pure...
为什么还操那个女服务员
...then why'd you fuck that waitress?
我搞砸了 好吗
I fucked up, all right.
我第二天就戒了酒 不是吗
And I quit the booze the next day, didn't I?
是的
Yeah.
不禁注意到你最近又开戒了
I can't help but notice you've been quitting the quitting lately.
你一直说
You know, you keep saying
做这一切都是为了纪念贝嘉
that you're doing all this to honor Becca's memory.
她活着的时候 你没对她这么上心呀
You never did that when she was alive.
所以 你不觉得应该停止扯谎了吗
So, don't you think it's time to cut the shit?
滚蛋吧 贱人
Fuck off, cunt.
没什么问题 不过 厕所里有用过的卫生棉条
All clear. Except for literal used tampons in the toilet.
美国特勤局
伙计们 特勤局的文件
Guys... Secret Service files.
1月6日的任务详情
Detail assignments for January 6th.
什么
What?
华盛顿露天市场的地图 辛格尔要在那里举行集会
It's a map of the D.C. Fairgrounds where Singer's having his rally.
他们要在那里刺杀总统 M说得没错
That's where they're giving him the old Dealey Plaza. M was right.
受保护者:当选总统罗伯特辛格尔
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
谢天谢地 你们来了
Oh, thank God you're here.
他杀了我丈夫
He killed my husband.
他关了我好几天了
He held me for days.
等等 你是...
Wait. Are you...?
是的
Yeah.
我是 你好
Yeah, hi.
天哪 你身上好烫 你没事吧
Oh, my God. You are... burning up. Are you okay?
里面热得像个熔炉  -好
It's like a furnace in there.  -Okay.
我们找人帮你 好吗
Let's get you some help. Yeah?
来吧
Come on.
该死 他妈的 她划伤了我 他妈的
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Fuck! Stop!
什么东西  -好恶心
What the fuck?  -So gross.
妈的 看到像她的人了吗  -没有
Fuck! Do you see anything?  -No.
该死的变形超人类
Fucking Supe shapeshifters.
恨死那些贱人了
I hate those cunts.
不过不得不称赞智者
Got to hand it to Sage though--
刺杀任务的完美人选
perfect choice for the job.
等等 所以 枪手变成什么样子都有可能
Wait, wait, wait. So we're saying that they could be anyone?
如果是这样 我们怎么救总统
How the fuck are we supposed to save the president if the killer could be anyone?
不慌不忙地救
By not shitting our panties.
休伊 等一下
Hughie, wait a minute.
天哪 你得去缝针
Oh, my God. You need stitches.
我会去急诊室 好吗  -我陪你去
I'll go to urgent care, okay?  -I'll go with you.
不 回公寓去 趁枪手回来之前 拿到那些计划 好吗
No, no, um, go back up there, get those plans before... whoever gets back, all right?
我稍后再联系你
I'll catch up with you later.
好 我爱你  -爱你
Okay. I love you.  -Love you.
打印出来的登机牌
Printed-out boarding pass?
你多大 87岁吗
Damn, what are you, 87?
你他妈的来这儿干什么  -我正要问你呢
The fuck are you doing here?  -You took the words right out of my mouth.
我之前去了枪手那里
See, I ran by that shithole earlier.
我看到了布彻尔 休伊 星光
I saw Butcher, Hughie and Starlight going in.
但某个混蛋却没现身
But one motherfucker was conspicuously absent.
所以...
So...
你要一走了之
this is it?
你以为我不想去伯利兹享清福
You think I don't want to just peace out to Belize,
喝杯代基里酒 找当地美女上床
sip a daiquiri, smash the local talent?
那就去买打折机票吧 混蛋  -嘿
Get on Priceline then, motherfucker.  -Hey.
这事还没完
This shit ain't over.
对我来说结束了
It's over for me.
我付出得够多了
I've given enough.
也许我他妈的值得去享享清福
Maybe I deserve to be fucking happy.
我送你去急诊室时 看到一个孩子
You know, when I carried your ass to the ER, there was a kid there.
他的眼神里充满敬畏
His eyes were like... "Holy shit."
看着我...
Looking at me...
好像我是位英雄
...like I was a hero.
没有尖叫的粉丝 没有摄像机
There were no screaming fans, no cameras.
甚至没有人知道
Nobody even knew.
除了这个孩子
Except for this one kid.
那感觉比我在沃特 做过的所有事情都要美好
That felt better than anything that I'd ever done at Vought.
因为这一次 我没有讨厌自己
Because for once... I didn't hate myself.
那要归功于你
That's on you.
火车头 你不明白 是吗 伙计
A-Train, you don't get it, do you, man?
我们参与的这场战斗
This fight that we're in?
他妈的永远不会结束
This never fucking ends.
它害死了我父亲 害死了我爷爷
It killed my father. It killed his father.
看看它把我变成了什么样
And look at what it's doing to me.
让我痛苦不堪 重蹈我爸和我爷的覆辙
It's tearing me the fuck apart. Just like it did them.
照镜子时 我再也认不出自己来了
You know, I look in the mirror... and I don't even see myself no more.
我已经一无所有了
I got nothing left.
只有家人
Except my family.
你认为祖国人 沃特
You think Homelander and Vought...
还有这些烂事不会影响到伯利兹吗
...and all of this shit ain't coming to Belize?
不会影响到整个世界
This whole fucking world?
那时 你的家人要去哪里
Where's your family gonna go then?
谢谢
Thanks.
等你吃完我们再调整离心次数
After you eat, we'll adjust your centrifugation numbers.
我想 也许 我们应该尝试甘油梯度
I think peut-être we should try a glycerol gradient.
这个...“实验室” 无法制造出他想要的东西
This, uh... quote-unquote "lab" can't produce what he wants.
是我们都想要的东西
What we all want.
我们都想干掉祖国人 不是吗
Homelander... [clicks tongue] fini, do we not?
你在最好的实验室工作过
You know, you worked in the finest lab
那里拥有最好的设备 可我呢
with the best equipment, but moi?
我曾在肮脏的地下室里工作过
I have worked in filthy basements with equipment
用的是从垃圾箱和一元店淘来的设备
from dumpsters and dollar stores.
必要性是促成发明的第一要素
Necessity is the MILF of invention.
知道嘛 他对着空气说话
You know, um, he would talk to people who weren't here.
你的那位朋友
Your friend.
或许可以听点音乐
Some music, perhaps?
我注意到你很享受20世纪90年代 令人反感的垃圾音乐
I noticed you enjoy truly revolting garbage from the 1990s.
♪ Come, my lady, come, come, my lady...
帮你工作 祝你胃口大开
Help you work. Bon appétit.
这种病毒
This virus.
♪ Sugar baby, such a sexy, sexy...
只给祖国人用 对吧  不会用在维琪身上
It's just for Homelander, right? Not for Vicky?
♪ You got me sprung with your tongue ring, and I ain't gonna lie ♪
♪ 'Cause your loving gets me high, so to keep you by my side...
莱恩 是爸爸
Ryan, it's Dad.
听着 儿子 最近太忙了 我很抱歉
Hey, listen, buddy, I-I'm sorry I've been so busy lately,
但我听说你不大同意拍那个
but I hear you're having some issues
布偶戏...的节目
with the-the puppet show thing.
我手头上事情很多 儿子 所以
Um, look, I got a lot going on here, buddy, so, uh,
帮我个忙 不要抱怨 拍就是了 好吗 为了我
do me a favor, just-just-just suck it up and-and do it, all right? For me.
太好了 爱你 很好 再见
Terrific. Love you. Great. Bye.
你绝对确定他就是泄密者
Are you absolutely sure that he is the leak?
那小混球都招了 什么都承认了
The little shit broke wide open. He confessed to everything.
先生  -网络喷子
Sir.  -Webweaver.
搞什么
Ew, what the fuck?
对不起 我一紧张就这样
I'm sorry. Happens when I'm nervous.
不用紧张 说吧 告诉他你跟我说过的话
Ain't got to be nervous, just... go on, tell him what you told me.
我知道
I know.
是 女士
Yes, ma'am.
是 先生
Yes, sir.
我知无不言
Whatever you want to know.
怎么运作的
How does it work?
战衣上有个洞 网就可以喷出去...
There's a hole in the suit so the webs can get out--
不 跟威廉布彻尔是怎么运作的
No. No. How does it work with William Butcher?
这个嘛 他...来找我
Yeah, well, uh... He-he... he comes to me.
我告诉他他想知道的事情
I tell him what he wants to know.
老天爷呀
Oh, for God sakes.
真令人尴尬  -他妈的闭嘴吧
That's just embarrassing.  -Just shut the fuck up.
布彻尔的一名下属穿着你 令人作呕的战衣去了泰克骑士的庄园
Now, one of Butcher's crew was wearing your nasty-ass suit to Tek-Knight's.
战衣是你给他的吗
Did you give it to them?
我万分羞愧
I'm not proud of it.
看吧
There it is.
帮我搞清楚一件事
Help me out with something here.
在那之前的几周 你怎么知道 我在哪里见维多利亚纽曼
Few weeks back, how did you know where I was meeting Victoria Neuman?
听着 我搞砸了 我知道
Look, I-I messed up. I know, I know...
对不起
I'm sorry.
Oh, God. I'm sorry.
我感觉很难受
I... I don't feel very good.
但你见过这个英国人吧
You ever meet this British guy?
他是个骗子
He's a liar.
把人搞得精神崩溃
He fucks with your brain.
也许是你意志薄弱  -是的 薄弱
Feeble brains, maybe.  -Yes. Feeble.
我脑子进水了
I'm all fucked up.
我给您制造了麻烦
I screwed you.
我非常 非常抱歉
I'm so, so sorry.
我会让您感到骄傲的 我向上帝发誓
I'll make you proud. I swear to God.
伙计 我拿你怎么办呢
Oh, buddy, what am I gonna do with you?
天哪 别拉了
Jesus. Oh, stop.
等等
Wait, wait!
什么  -不是我干的
What?  -It wasn't me.
求你了
No, please.
谢谢你 鞭炮
Thank you, Firecracker.
没问题
You bet.
圣诞快乐 一份小小心意
For Noel. It's not much.
我很想念你
I've missed you.
我每天都去 可你不肯见我
I came every day. You wouldn't see me.
我很惭愧
I was ashamed.
因为你对科林和他家人所做的一切
For what you did to Colin and his family.
你向安妮倾诉了很多 其余的都是我拼凑起来的
You told a lot to Annie. The rest I pieced together.
那你就知道我为什么要自首了
Then you know why I had to turn myself in.
你累了
You're exhausting.
对不起
Sorry.
你总是这样 喜怒无常
You always do this. All moody.
折磨自己
Torturing yourself.
不然我该怎样
What else was I supposed to do?
寻求帮助 找我帮你
Ask for help. Come to me for help.
你无能为力 你不理解
You can't help. You don't understand.
你知道我为什么不能说话吗
Do you know why I can't speak?
你看着闪光军杀了亲生父母
You watched Shining Light kill your parents.
你弟弟告诉我的
Your brother told me.
我从来没有告诉健二真相
I never told Kenji the truth.
我在营地的第一个晚上
It was my first night at the camp.
我们像幽灵一样移动
We move like ghosts.
寂静无声
In silence.
你们也一样
So will you.
第一个哭出来的女孩
So the first girl to cry out?
就输了
She loses.
准备好了吗
You ready?
我无声无息地杀了她
I murdered her without making a sound.
后来允许我说话了
Then when I was allowed to speak again...
可我说不出来了
I couldn't.
当时你别无选择
You did not have a choice.
我当然有选择
Of course I did.
让他们杀了我 总比我对那个女孩做的事强
Better they kill me, than what I did to that girl.
比我对很多女孩做的事都强
What I did to lots of girls.
我看着镜子里的自己 感到无比厌恶
I look in the mirror and hate what I see.
所以我比你想象的
So I understand,
更理解你的感受
more than you know.
你不应该恨自己
You should not hate yourself.
那你也不应该
Then neither should you.
我们怎么可能原谅自己
How can we possibly forgive ourselves?
我们怎样才能继续活下去
How can we move on?
病毒准备就绪时 我们应该释放他 不是吗
When the virus is ready, we should set him free, no?
布彻尔会不高兴的
Butcher won't be happy.
那这一定是正确的做法
Then it must be the right thing to do.
宝贝 是你吗  -是的 宝贝
Babe, that you?  -Yeah, babe.
你能给我买些生鱼片吗
Can you pick me up some Sugarfish?
不行 我们已经讨论过这事了
No. We've talked about this.
我不能参与屠杀长鳍金枪鱼
I can't take part in the slaughter of albacore.
我有个最好的朋友就是长鳍金枪鱼
One of my ride-or-dies is an albacore.
好吧 所以我既不能待在想待的地方 也不能吃想吃的东西
Okay, so I don't get to stay where I want or eat what I want.
这话什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
“有时 怎样获得就怎样失去”
"Sometimes the way you get them is the way you lose them."
为什么引用丽莎范德庞普的话  -我知道
Why are you quoting Lisa Vanderpump?
智者的事
I know about Sage.
说什么呢 智者
What are you talking about? Sage?
别以为假装对我好 就能瞒天过海 凯文
Don't patronize me, Kevin.
我已经知道一段时间了
I've known for a while.
你们幽会之后 在你身上 我的吸盘能感受到她的味道
My suckers can smell her on you after your trysts.
就像现在这样
Like the one you're coming from now.
我真的很爱你
I love you so much.
你温柔的心 你无畏的写作
Your gentle heart, your fearless writing.
你能诚实地说她像我一样爱你吗
Can you honestly say she feels the same?
我现在不知道该怎么跟你说  -试着说实话
Look, I don't know what to tell you right now.  -Try the truth.
还不算太晚
It's not too late.
这份爱值得为之奋斗 我们的爱值得为之奋斗
This is worth fighting for. We're worth fighting for.
智者根本不可能像我这么关心你
There's no way Sage cares about you the way that I do.
她说我是高人一等的生物
She says that I'm a superior being,
她是人类  -这不公平
and she has four limbs.  -That is not fair.
情况如此 无可奈何
Yeah, well, it is what it is.
这是句愚蠢 空洞的话 说这话的是...
That's a dumb, nothing phrase, spoken by--
愚蠢的人
Dumb people? Dumb people?
你残酷无情时令我讨厌
I hate it when you get nasty.
我有什么选择 谈敏感问题时 你根本不顾及我的感受
Well, what choice do I have, when you're rubbing my face in it?
我享乐一次 有什么大不了的
Oh, what, that I'm happy for once?!
对不起  -我为你感到遗憾
I'm sorry!  -I feel sorry for you.
为我感到遗憾 看看你那副德行
For me? For me? Look at you.
你意识到她并不尊重你时就不会笑了
You won't be laughing when you realize she doesn't respect you.
但她确实尊重我
She does respect me!
醒醒吧 凯文 她在利用你
Wake up, Kevin. She's using you.
闭嘴  -你正在为了一个
You shut the fuck up!  -You're throwing us away for a woman
认为你很可悲的女人损耗我们的感情
who thinks you're pathetic...
凯文
Kevin! Kevin!
Come back!
回来 求你了 凯文 求你了
Please, Kevin, please.
求你了 凯文
Please, Kevin.
凯文 我...我无法呼吸
Kevin, I-I-I can't breathe.
求你...  -什么
Please...  -What?
天哪  -凯文 求你了
Oh, my God. Kevin! Please!
他妈的
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
凯文
Kevin!
开门  -妈的
Open the door!  -Fuck.
我爱...你
I love... you.
好
Okay.
喂 深海
Deep?
深海
你都明白了吗  -是的 先生
Did you get all that?  -Yes, sir.
我现在终于清楚了  -好的
I finally have clarity now.  -Good.
你想杀谁 我就去杀 随时听你派遣
I will kill whoever you want me to kill, whenever you want me
你一声令下 我就会杀死海洋里所有该死的鱼
to kill them. I'll kill every goddamn fish in the ocean if you say so.
好
Okay.
好样的
Attaboy.
去做吧
Well, get to it.
当选副总统女士  -在呢
Madam Vice President-elect?  -Yeah?
有人来见您
There's someone here to see you.
我会很想念纽约的杂货店
Fuck, I'm gonna miss New York bodegas.
听着 我们需要谈谈
Listen, we need to talk.
你仍然可以阻止这一切 罢手吧
You can still stop all this, all right? Just stop.
想让我改变主意 你肯定是黔驴技穷了
You must be pretty desperate if you're throwing a Hail Mary like this. Jesus--
五分钟 可以吗
Five minutes, all right?
不说废话 我们俩好好谈谈 情况有多么糟糕
Just five minutes where we cut the bullshit and we talk, just you and me, about how fucked all this is.
这是政治
What it is, is politics.
你知道的 为达目的求同存异罢了
You know how it goes, strange bedfellows.
这可不是在跟米特罗姆尼合作
Yeah, but it's not like you're palling around with Mitt Romney.
你在跟祖国人合作
You're working with Homelander.
他要刺杀总统 这话从我嘴里说出来 听起来难以置信
He's gonna kill the president. That sounds fucking insane coming out of my mouth.
祖国人把星光追随者们都关进拘留营
And when Homelander chucks all the Starlighters into internment camps, you're just,
你也觉得无所谓吗
you're cool with that, too?
你对拘留营一无所知
You didn't know about the camps.
你觉得为什么自己 被请到了泰克骑士庄园
Why do you think that you were at Tek-Knight's?
要用他的监狱做拘留营  -我得接着打包了
That's what his prisons are for.  -I got to get back to it.
我手上还有对你不利的证据
I still have all the dirt on you.
你在泰克骑士庄园里说的话 每一个字
What you said at Tek-Knight's. Everything.
这是威胁吗
Is that a threat?
不是
No.
因为我们一发布 你就会杀了我们所有人
Because when we drop it, then you'll kill us all.
像你说的 肯定会两败俱伤
Like you said, mutually assured destruction.
但并非一定要两败俱伤
But it doesn't have to be that way.
如果你还尚存一丝人性 就像从前的你
And if you're even, like, one percent of the person that I knew,
那么 我认为你并不想这样做
then I don't think you really want to do this.
你还来得及罢手 维琪 现在还不算太晚
You can still step back. Vic, it's not too late.
感谢你过来见我
Thanks for coming by.
你父亲的事
I'm sorry...
我很遗憾
...to hear about your dad.
休伊还是不接电话
Hughie's still not answering.
我很担心他
I'm worried about him.
还好吗 小可爱
Sup, cum burgers?
你他妈的怎么来了
The fuck you doing here?
祖国人受够你了 兄弟
Homelander is sick of your shit, bro.
说要帮你脱离苦海
Said to put you out of your misery.
所以派了你来
And he sent you?
看来给章鱼舔屄还不够你忙的
Sure you ain't too busy tongue lashing your octo-pussy?
才没有 我从没...
What? No. I never...
他不光派了我来
He didn't just send me.
知道吗
Do you know what?
我不敢相信自己会说这种话 但现在是圣诞节
I can't believe I'm saying this, but it's Christmas.
你们两个笨蛋赶快逃吧
You two twats leg it right now,
我们会忘记你们来过这里  -什么 伙计
and we'll forget you was ever here.  -What, dude?
我几乎听不懂你说话 你的口音太重了
I can barely understand you, your accent's insane.
你到底想要怎样 深海
What the fuck do you want, Deep?
讨个正义 你个婊子
Justice, you fucking bitch.
天哪 我会非常享受杀掉你
God, I'm gonna enjoy this so much.
首先 你想害我被封杀
First, you tried to cancel me,
陷害我这个无辜者
victimize an innocent man because I guess
因为现在 这样对待白人男性会显得很酷
that's just cool to do to white guys nowadays.
结果你自食其果
But joke's on you.
“我也是”反性骚扰运动已经终结了 毫无结果
#MeToo's over, sweetheart, it didn't work. Wah-wah-wah.
我觉得你说的并不是真相
I do not respect your truth.
我不尊重 也不珍惜你的故事
I do not honor and cherish your story.
我他妈的才不会道歉呢
And I do not fucking apologize.
这傻逼有嗜睡症
Cunt's narcoleptic.
凯斯勒 无论你对以西结做了什么
Kessler, whatever you did to Ezekiel,
再做一遍
do it again.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
等等 你是...泄密者
Wait, are you... You're the leak?
他说话了
Did he just talk?
兄弟
Bro,
是你吗 兄弟
it was you, bro?
深海 告诉你一声 我一直...
Deep, just FYI, I have always,
一直都很讨厌你
always fucking hated your ass.
他妈的 你会飞
Fuck, he can fly?
叫你好看 傻...
Eat a flying dick, motherfuck--
玄色很快就回来了 我们快走吧
Noir will be back up here in no time, so let's go.
他就在这儿 我们干掉他吧
He's right fucking there. Let's do him.
你知道怎么干掉他吗 布彻尔  我可不知道
You know how, Butcher? 'Cause I don't,
但玄色肯定知道怎么干掉我们
but Noir sure as hell's gonna know how to fucking kill us.
所以还是快走吧
Now, come the fuck on.
亚莉克莎 播放戴夫马修斯的 平静混音音乐
Alexa, play "Dave Matthews Chill Mix." Playing Dave Matthews--
亚莉克莎 求你别播  -火车头 搞什么
Alexa, please fucking don't.  -What the fuck, A-Train?
听着 我们得走了 现在就走
Listen, we got to go, now.
深海和玄色知道我是泄密者了  -等等 什么
Deep and Noir know that I'm the leak.  -Wait, what?
祖国人很快就会知道  -该死的混蛋 你有说过我的事吗
Homelander's about to find out any second.  -Did you say anything about me, you fucking asshole?
当然没有 我什么也没说
No, of course not. I didn't say anything.
火车头 搞什么  -艾诗丽
A-Train, what the fuck? What the fuck?  -Ashley.
这是我们的机会
This is our chance.
失不再来
佛罗伦萨 哪里都行
Florence, anywhere,
但我们这就得走
but let's go.
我不能走
I can't.
那你自便吧  -等等
Suit yourself.  -Wait, wait.
你的芯片
Your chip.
别忘了把它取出来
Don't forget to cut it out.
♪ Well, it's Christmastime ♪
♪ And the family's near...
不好意思 你是星光 对吧
Hi, sorry, you're Starlight, right?
我可以...拍张自拍吗  -好的
Can I just get a selfie?  -Uh, okay.
拍得很好  -好
Oh, that's a good one.  -Okay.
谢谢  -谢谢
Thank you.  -Thanks.
要怎么办 M
So what's it gonna be, M?
你要帮我们阻止暗杀和暴力叛乱
You gonna help us stop an assassination, a violent insurrection?
还是说会置之不理
Or you off to have a wank?
♪ Merry Christmas, baby...
看来是要置之不理
Looks like a wank then.
凯斯勒是谁
Who's Kessler?
凯斯勒
Kessler?
在办公室大楼里
In the Flatiron.
你喊了一个名字 “凯斯勒” 说了些跟以西结有关的事情
You shouted a name, "Kessler," and something that had to do with Ezekiel.
那是怎么回事
What was that?
不知道你在说些什么 亲爱的
No idea what you're on about there, luv.
你真的不来了
You're really not coming.
只好以后再喝朗姆潘趣酒了 宝贝
Those rum punches are gonna have to wait, babe.
珍妮需要你
Janine needs you.
亲爱的 我别无所求 只有一个目标
Monique, the one thing I've wanted more than anything,
我每晚都祈祷它会实现
my one prayer every night,
就是再次跟你和珍妮成为一家人
has been to be with you and Janine again. To be a family.
但如果我不得不这样保护你们俩 我就无法实现这个目标
But if I'm gonna protect you two the way I have to, I can't.
我就...
I just...
做不到
I can't.
也许某天会实现
Maybe one day.
也许
"Maybe"?
“也许”是什么意思 马文
What the hell's that supposed to mean, Marvin? Maybe?
我得挂了 宝贝  -马文 等等
I got to go, babe.  -Marvin, wait--
祖国人
Homelander?
你没事吧
Are you all right?
火车头
A-Train?
他怎么可以这样对我
How could he do this to me?
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你知道 有些人就是...
You know, some folks are just...
他们生来就傲慢自负
...well, they're born uppity.
他在哪里
Where is he?
他取出了追踪芯片
He cut out his tracking chip.
他的家人也消失了
And his family's gone, too.
当然
Of course.
你派了深海和玄色去杀布彻尔
You sent Deep and Noir after Butcher?
我们讨论过这事
We talked about this.
世界上最聪明的人 却不知道火车头是泄密者
Smartest person in the world, and you didn't know A-Train was the leak?
我知道
I knew.
你知道
You knew.
却让我们无缘无故地杀死网络喷子
And you let us kill Webweaver for nothing?
妈的
Oh, shit.
你们杀了网络喷子
You killed Webweaver?
你们以为他是泄密者
Did you think he was the leak?
他这个瘾君子 只要能让他回家接着吸毒
He was a junkie who'd confess to nailing Christ on the cross
把基督钉在十字架上这种事 他都会承认
if it got him home for his next fix.
我说得很清楚
I was very clear.
别再隐藏秘密了
No more secrets.
但火车头只是泄露了
But A-Train only leaked
我想让布彻尔及其团队知道的信息
exactly the information I wanted Butcher and his team to know.
在此之前 他一直都是传递错误信息的完美人选
He was the perfect misinformation delivery system. Until now.
这都是计划的一部分
This was all part of the plan.
好吧
Okay.
滚吧 你走人吧
Get the fuck out of here. You're done.
回到你在底特律的小垃圾公寓里 孤独地死去吧
Go back to your little litter box in Detroit and die alone.
我...你答应过的 你答应过我你会听我的
You promised. You promised me you would listen to me.
我没把你大卸八块寄回家 已经算你走运了
You're lucky I'm not sending you home in a bucket.
滚
Go.
好吧
Fine,
身边只留下她这种人
surround yourself with people like her.
你可以系统地消除任何妨碍你的人
Then you can systematically eliminate anyone who gets in your way,
但有一个人 你永远无法打败
but there's one person you will never, ever defeat.
没了我 祝你好运
Good luck without me.
我们不需要她
We don't need her.
出...出去
Just-just get out.
你确定
Are you sure there's...
没有我能为你做的事吗
...nothing I can... do for you?
确定
No.
快滚出去吧  -好
Oh, just get the fuck out.  -Okay.
兄弟
Bro?
Bro!
兄弟
Bro?
Bro.
是的
Yeah
兄弟
Bro.
你好呀
Hey, you.
我们今天很不顺
Hey, so we've had a day.
等等 急什么  -祖国人
Wait, what's the rush?  -Homelander.
他解雇了我
He fired me.
等等 但你不能离开 我爱你
Wait, but you can't leave. I love you.
我们有真感情 不是吗  -等等
We have something special, don't we?  -Wait.
她对自己进行脑白质切除术后 也操你吗
Is she lobotomizing herself to fuck you, too?
她没做什么脑白质切除术啊
What do you mean, "lobotomizing herself"?
兄弟
Bro.
♪ I was lying on the grass of Sunday morning... ♪
你是对的
You were right. It's ready.
准备好了
The glycerol gradient.
甘油梯度
Uh, it worked.
即使在一个破烂的实验室里也有效
Even in a shitty lab.
进行眼底荧光素血管造影测试后 如果病毒发挥作用
After we do an FFA test, see that the virus is working,
我们就要告诉你个好消息 我的朋友
we have some good news for you, mon ami.
喜美子
Kimiko.
不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
♪ Making sure I'm not in too deep...
♪ If you steal my sunshine...
没关系
Okay. It's okay.
心肝 看着我
Mon coeur, look at me.
抓住这个 专心看这个
Take this. Focus on this.
对不起
I'm sorry!
♪ In the park across the street ♪
♪ L-A-T-E-R that week ♪
♪ My sticky paws were into making straws out of big fat slurpy treats ♪
♪ An incredible eight-food heap...
你是蜜蜂的膝盖
? An incredible eight-food heap...
♪ But I invite who I want to come ♪
♪ So I missed a million miles of fun...
没关系
It's okay.
你没事
You're okay.
嘿 你没事
Yeah. You're okay.
♪ If you steal my sunshine ♪
而你却没有意识到萨米尔想跑
You didn't twig to what Sameer was up to?
被锁得那么牢
Well, with bindings so thick,
他一定是已经准备了好几天 也许好几周 不是吗
he must have worked them for days. Maybe weeks. No?
好吧
All right. All right.
重要的是 如果萨米尔能从死羊身上提取出病毒
What matters is if Sameer can get the bug out of a sheep's head,
法兰奇就可以 从喜美子的断腿里提取出病毒
Frenchie can get it out of Kimiko's gam.
我们知道病毒是有效的
All right, so, we know the virus works,
但它足够强大吗
but is it strong enough?
足以杀死祖国人吗
To kill Homelander?
杀不死 但杀死纽曼
No. But to kill Neuman at least?
是有可能的
C'est possible.
好几个星期了 结果只是个“可能”
We've been on this for weeks, and all we have is a maybe?
各位
Yo...
为什么都板着脸
Why all the grim faces?
以前比这糟糕 但我们都挺过来了
We've done more with less.
我们绝不容许任何人暗杀总统
Ain't nobody gonna murk the president, not on our fuckin' watch.
法兰奇 病毒不会凭空出现 兄弟
Frenchie, that virus--it ain't gonna cook itself, brother.
开工啦
All right, let's go.
快点 混蛋们
Chop, chop, motherfuckers.
莱恩 是爸爸
Ryan, it's Dad.
听着 儿子 最近太忙了 我很抱歉
Hey, listen, buddy, I-I'm sorry I've been so busy lately,
但我听说你不大同意拍那个
but I hear you're having some issues with the-
布偶戏...的节目
the puppet show thing.
我手头上事情很多 儿子 所以
Um, look, I got a lot going on here, buddy, so, uh, do me a favor.
帮我个忙 不要抱怨 拍就是了 好吗 为了我
Just-just suck it up and-and do it. All right? For me.
太好了 爱你 很好 再见
Terrific. Love you. Great. Bye.
♪ When you see something, say something ♪
发现可疑情况就举报 致电1-800-1 沃特
? When you see something, say something ? ? Call 1-800-1-Vought ?
♪ Call 1-800-1-Vought ♪
♪ Could be a moocher from the welfare state ♪
可能是攫取福利的贪婪者
? Could be a moocher from the welfare state ?
♪ Or your teacher who tries to indoctrinate ♪
也可能是老师想要灌输什么
? Or your teacher who tries to indoctrinate ?
♪ A socialist who says the stars and stripes aren't great ♪
或是社会主义者说美国不伟大
? A socialist who says the stars and stripes aren't great ?
竖起耳朵 仔细观察
? Keep your ears open and your eyes stay peeled ?
♪ Keep your ears open and your eyes stay peeled ♪
但无论怎样 别闭口不言
? But whatever you do, make sure your lips aren't sealed ?
♪ But whatever you do, make sure your lips aren't sealed ♪
♪ When you see something, say something ♪
发现可疑情况就举报
? When you see something, say something ?
♪ Pick up the phone and make the call ♪
拿起电话拨打号码
? Pick up the phone and make the call ?
♪ When you see something, say something ♪
发现可疑情况就举报
? When you see something, say something ?
超人类为我们创造安全的世界
? Supes make the world a safe place for us all...
♪ Supes make the world a safe place for us all...
他来了
There he is.
我需要你的时候 你他妈的在哪里
Where the fuck were you when I needed you?
沉默对待是双向的
Silent treatment goes both ways.
♪ Could be the scientist who makes vaccines ♪
可能是制造疫苗的科学家
? Could be the scientist who makes vaccines ?
♪ The guy with a beard who's a beauty queen ♪
那个长着胡子的变装皇后
? The guy with a beard who's a beauty queen ?
♪ The immigrant who keeps your...
移民不停地...
? The immigrant who keeps your...
停下来 快...停下来
Stop. Stop. Just stop.
这首歌不行
This song isn't cool.
老实说 这些都不行
Honestly, none of this is cool.
快他妈的切广告
Go to fucking commercial!
不 不要切广告
No. Don't go to commercial.
继续拍 拜托了
Keep rolling, please.
你的家人不是敌人
Your family isn't your enemy.
你的家人是你的全部
Your family is all you've got.
最近我总在想我妈
I've been thinking about my mom a lot lately.
她死了
She died.
但她很喜欢圣诞节
But she loved Christmas.
喜欢用锐滋糖果做的棉花糖夹心饼干
And s'mores with Reese's.
喜欢看《母女情深》
And Terms of Endearment.
她爱自己的丈夫比利
And she loved her husband Billy.
但她不会喜欢这个布偶节目
But she wouldn't love this.
她不会希望我拍这个
She wouldn't want me doing it.
我妈总是告诉我要说实话
My mom always told me to tell the truth...
因此...
...which is why...
对不起
I'm sorry.
这就是为何我对这孩子充满信心
And that... is why I got faith in the kid,
太他妈的让我骄傲了
you little fucking beauty.
混蛋
Wanker.
打911
Call 911!
安妮
Hey, Annie?
其实 我今天没去急诊室
I, uh... I didn't actually go to urgent care today.
我看得出来
Yeah, I could tell.
是的
Yeah.
我去找维琪了  -休伊
Well, I... I went to go see Vicky.  -Hughie!
我知道 那样做...
Yeah, look, I know it...
我没事 只是...
I'm okay. It's just...
我不知道 我想也许 自己可以说服她罢手 或者...
I don't know. I thought maybe I could talk her out of it, or...
结果呢
And...?
是什么让你...
what made you--
我只是想试试
I-I... just thought I would... try it on.
好吧 感觉怎么样
Okay. How-How's it... feel?
感觉很烦人
Feels annoying...
因为你是对的
that you were right.
我们一步一步来 一次处理一个麻烦
We'll take it... step by step, one dumpster fire at a time.
所以 你是说我给出了天才的建议
So, you're saying, I give genius advice.
别太得意了
Don't push it.
现在
Now...
承认吧
admit it.
你留下战衣时 幻想过这一幕
You have fantasized about... keeping this suit on for this.
我并非没有幻想过
I haven't... not fantasized about it.
不
No
♪ When you see something, say something ♪
♪ Report that groomer when he comes for you ♪
♪ See something, say something ♪
♪ 'Cause he hates America and Christmas, too ♪
♪ It's the woke principal and his husband Chad ♪
♪ Or could be your uncle who says Supes are bad ♪
♪ It might even be your mom and your dad ♪
♪ But listen to the golden rule ♪
♪ If you see something, say something ♪
♪ Call 1-800-1-Vought ♪
♪ Could be a moocher from the welfare state ♪
♪ Or your teacher who tries to indoctrinate ♪
♪ A socialist who says the stars and stripes aren't great ♪
♪ Keep your ears open and your eyes stay peeled ♪
♪ But whatever you do, make sure your lips aren't sealed ♪
♪ When you see something, say something ♪
♪ Pick up the phone and make the call ♪
♪ Supes make the world a safe place for us all ♪
♪ It might be the people who don't trust the cops ♪
♪ Or when Sean Penn says that Supes should stop ♪
♪ It might even be your mom and your pops ♪
♪ But don't forget the golden rule ♪
♪ If you see something, say something ♪
♪ Call 1-800-1-Vought ♪
♪ Could be the scientist who makes vaccines ♪
♪ The guy with the beard who's a beauty queen ♪
♪ The immigrant who keeps your apartment clean ♪
♪ Keep your ears open and your eyes stay peeled ♪
♪ But whatever you do, make sure your lips aren't sealed ♪
♪ Put them on the naughty list ♪
♪ We can't let those commies win ♪
♪ So when you see someone who's looking suss ♪
♪ Just turn those losers in ♪
♪ When you see something, say something ♪
♪ Report that groomer when he comes for you ♪
♪ See something, say something ♪
♪ 'Cause he hates America and Christmas, too ♪
♪ It's probably those who don't believe in God ♪
♪ And anyone who thinks that Supes are a fraud ♪
♪ So tell them all the golden rule ♪
♪ If you see something, say something ♪
♪ Call 1-800-1-Vought ♪
♪ And you'll be a hero, too ♪